ideaconnection.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy

* * *

* * *

  * ### Solution Seekers

  * Risk-Free Innovation:  
Have Experts Solve your Problems Now
  * Crisis Help
  * ### Problem Solvers

  * Solve Problems for Pay
  * ### Free Services

  * Post Technology for License
  * View Technology for License
  * Post Technology Wanted
  * View Technology Wanted
  * Sell Inventions
  * Buy Inventions
  * Post Funding Request
  * View Funding Requests
  * Post Problems for the Common Good
  * View Problems for the Common Good
  * Be a Mentor
  * Find a Mentor
  * Facilitators Wanted
  * ### Resources

  * Innovation Authors
  * Corporate Innovators
  * Inspirational Books
  * Right Brain Workouts
  * New Inventions
  * Innovative Conferences
  * Idea Contests
  * Innovation News
  * Videos
  * Idea Blog
  * Other Resources
  * ### Company

  * For Consultants
  * Sales Personnel Wanted
  * News Releases
  * Media Room
  * Advisors
  * FAQ
  * Terms of Service
  * Privacy Policy
  * About the Company
  * Innovation Newsletter
  * Link to Us
  * Sales People Wanted
  * Sitemap
  * Contact Us

 |    
This Privacy Policy explains what Online Data Services Ltd. ("ODS"), doing business as _IdeaConnection.com_ ("IC") does with the personal information that is collected from users of the _IdeaConnection.com_ website. IC may change its policy from time to time, so it is suggested that you check this web site from time to time to ensure that you know about current policy. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact _IdeaConnection.com_ via our Contact Page.

IC may collect IP addresses to help understand how our audience uses our site and to gather broader demographic information, so that IC can make its site better and improve users' overall experience when they visit _IdeaConnection.com_. For these same reasons, if your browser is set up to accept them, IC uses a feature known as a "cookie." Cookies contain bits of information that websites transfer to your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site such as _IdeaConnection.com_. 

**Children**  
If you are under 18, you may not use this site.

**How IC Discloses Your Personal Information**  
IC will only disclose any personally identifiable information about individual users, in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service, or to comply with applicable laws or valid legal process, or to protect the rights or property of IC.

If you post an ides, IC discloses personally identifiable individual information and the other information you provide us to other members of the IC website. IC cannot guarantee that the information you submit to us will not end up in the hands of spammers.

IC may also disclose your contact information and the other information that you provide us in the following circumstances:

  1. IC may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. They may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but will not be able to legally use it for other purposes.
  2. IC might change, sell, reorganize or liquidate via bankruptcy this business. If so, your information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
  3. IC may release account and other personal information when IC believes release is appropriate to comply with law, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of IC, our users, or others. 

From time to time IC may also provide aggregate (statistical) information to third parties to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. If IC partners with another party to provide a specific service to you, and if you sign up for the service, then and only then will IC provide your other information to such partner.

**Our other Services**  
IC may send you occasional notices or newsletters about IC services, unless you tell us not to. If you do not want to receive such offers and mailings, you can click the unsubscribe link, which you will find on our email messages or send an email at any time via our Contact page.

When you submit an idea to _IdeaConnection.com_ , you will be sent a complimentary issue of our IC Newsletter, in order to keep you up to date with new developments and ideas on the website. If you do not wish to receive further issues, please use the unsubscribe link provided at the bottom of the Newsletter.

**How to Edit the Information IC Has About You**  
If you want to correct or change the information in your profile, or any other information we have about you, please login to your account and make the changes you wish.

The information you post with IC may be made available to the public. Furthermore, while we do our best to protect your personal information, IC cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Your contact information is not shared with anyone using the website.

IC may provide links from our website to others. If you follow these links from our site to theirs, you should be aware that these other sites have their privacy and data collection practices. IC has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies. For more information regarding a site and its privacy policies, check that site.

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can Contact Us.

**Conditions of Use**  
Any dispute over privacy is subject to our Terms of Service, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and the application of the law of British Columbia, Canada. While IC will endeavour to email you with changes to either this Privacy Statement or the Terms of Service, you should check our web site frequently for any recent changes.

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions or comments about the practices of this site, or your dealings with us, you may Contact Us.

|  | 

**FREE INNOVATION NEWSLETTER**  
  
---  
  
© 2002-2008 Online Data Services Ltd. All rights reserved.  
IdeaConnection and ThinkSpace are trade-marks of Online Data Services Ltd.
